[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the following Irish saying: If you want ______, always carry the back tooth of a horse with you.", "correct_answer": "money", "incorrect_answers": ["to go swimming", "beauty", "to be the life of the party"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Evan like in the film Superbad?", "correct_answer": "Becka", "incorrect_answers": ["Cindy", "Natalie", "Marry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This number is usually associated with the unknown and the bad luck. A fear of this number is known as triskaidekaphobia.", "correct_answer": "13", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "9", "666"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Michael Moore documentary?", "correct_answer": "An Inconvenient Truth", "incorrect_answers": ["Sicko", "Fahrenheit 9/11", "Bowling for Columbine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The folic acid, a compound especially important during periods of rapid cell division and growth, is commercially known under what name?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B9", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B7", "Vitamin B1", "Vitamin B12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Sophie have tattooed on her arm in the 1983 Academy Award-winning movie Sophies Choice?", "correct_answer": "A number", "incorrect_answers": ["A heart", "A dog", "A swastika"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the book Jurassic Park, the fictional island Isla Nublar, where recreated dinosaur species live, is situated in which part of the world?", "correct_answer": "Near Costa Rica", "incorrect_answers": ["Near Japan", "Near Chile", "Near Spain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the only woman taking part in the journey in the movie Journey to the Center of the Earth.", "correct_answer": "Carla", "incorrect_answers": ["Marion", "Gwendolyn", "Beatrice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the theropod dinosaur with a long head, flat snout, and large sickle-shaped claw on the second toe of each foot.", "correct_answer": "Velociraptor", "incorrect_answers": ["Stegosaurus", "Tyrannosaur", "Raptor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oh and remember, next Friday is Hawaiian shirt day. So, you know, if you want to, go ahead and wear a Hawaiian shirt and jeans is a quote from which of these films?", "correct_answer": "Office Space", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wedding Singer", "Napoleon Dynamite", "Good Luck Chuck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Star Wars character did the Kaminoans clone to make the clone army for the Republic?", "correct_answer": "Jango", "incorrect_answers": ["Greedo", "Boba", "Han Solo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the 56th Academy Awards in 1984, the Academy Award for Best Picture was given to this 1983 movie.", "correct_answer": "Terms of Endearment", "incorrect_answers": ["Tender Mercies", "The Big Chill", "The Right Stuff"]}]